Kristian Davis

Denver, CO 80203 nkzww4jn5k@privaterelay.appleid.com +1 303 505 0692

Professional Summary

Personable and dedicated customer service representative with extensive experience in leadership and adaptability. Solid team player with upbeat, positive attitude with proven skill in establishing rapport with clients. Able to proactively learn and apply new skills to meet evolving business needs. Motivated to maintain customer satisfaction. Articulate, enthusiastic and results-oriented with demonstrated passion for building relationships, cultivating partnerships and growing businesses. Demonstrates strong work ethic and a high-energy approach to tasks. Actively developing organizational strategies to optimize productivity

Work Experience

Floor Manager

X Bar-Denver, CO January 2017 to Present

- · Assigned tasks to team members in accordance with their skill set
- Developed strategies for increasing sales productivity and profitability within the department
- Coached team members on customer service techniques and provided feedback on performance
- Provided training and guidance to new employees regarding store policies and procedures

Bartender

X Bar-Denver, CO January 2017 to Present

- Greeted customers and provided excellent customer service
- · Maintained inventory of liquor, beer, wine, and other beverage items
- · De-escalated customer complaints in a professional manner
- Developed good working relationships with fellow employees through effective communication
- · Effectively multitasked within fast-paced environment

Education

High school diploma or GED in General Studies

Eagle Academy

August 2008 to August 2012

Skills

- Training & Development (10+ years)
- Employee Management (10+ years)

- Sales Training (10+ years)
- Conflict Resolution (8 years)
- Quickly mastering new tools, systems, and methodologies (10+ years)
- Maintain composure and productivity in high-stress settingd (8 years)